<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="p1_0">P1: 0</string>
    <string name="p2_0">P2: 0</string>
    <string name="sr_mostacho">Sr. Mostacho</string>
    <string name="rincon_28">Rincón 28</string>
    <string name="fruty">Fruty Yoghurt</string>
    <string name="nana_pancha">Nana Pancha</string>
    <string name="restaurant_plaza">Restaurante Plaza</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="ny_handicrafts">NY Crafts</string>
    <string name="crafts">Crafts</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="title">Tittle</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="info_corner">Do you meet Rincón 28 Pizza and Grill! Come on to our restaurant, we invite you to try the dish of the day.</string>
    <string name="info_mostacho">In the Mostacho you eat like at home ... but without having to wash the dishes. Come and have a new opportunity to know something new!</string>
    <string name="info_nana_pancha">Cooking with love feeds your soul and Nana Pancha is what we are looking for. Give yourself the opportunity to meet us.</string>
    <string name="info_restaurant_square">Eating or not eating is the question, do not question me and eat here. Come and know what we have for you</string>
    <string name="slide">Swipe up to view the images.</string>
    <string name="info_video_one">The following video shows where the Magic Town Dolores Hidalgo C.I.N. Gto., And the most famous places that can be found. The video is taken from YouTube and the copyright is respected: Copyright: Galleries TV</string>
    <string name="info_video_two">The following video shows where the Magic Town Dolores Hidalgo C.I.N. Gto., And the most famous places that can be found. The video is taken from YouTube and the copyright is respected: Copyright: Adolfo Campos</string>
    <string name="info_video_three">Between mountains and depressions of the mountains, the heart of our independent nation beats. The history of this magical town tells the transcendent events that led to the destiny of each Mexican. It has been more than two centuries since the priest Don Miguel Hidalgo y Costilla rang the bell, and his vibrant appeal is still felt in every corner of the town. In his parish, his temples, his haciendas, in every street where his inhabitants and his visitors walk every day. While enjoying a delicious snow, you are invited to feel this, your vibrant history. The video is taken from YouTube and the copyright is respected: Copyright: Guanajuato México</string>
    <string name="info_video_four">Know several tourist aspects of Dolores Hidalgo C.I.N. Guanajuato The video is taken from YouTube and the copyright is respected: Copyright: Turismo Dolores Hidalgo</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sing in</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="register_user">Register Usuario</string>
    <string name="get_out">get out</string>
    <string name="content">This video shows a bit about the culture that you have in Dolores Hidalgo CIN, Gto, its people, its churches, its history, there will not be a better place to know this history as it is in the Museum of the Casa de los Descendientes de Hidalgo, come and dare to live an unforgettable experience in this beautiful town</string>
    <string name="info_paint">Room 1 Paintings In this room you will find a great variety of paintings you will be able to see a copy of the most original portrait of Miguel Hidalgo y Costilla, since the original one is in the Alhondiga de Granaditas in Guanajuato.</string>
    <string name="info_photo_tour">Room 2 Photographs In this room you will find a great variety of photographs, one of them is one of high importance value since it is the christening certificate of Miguel Hidalgo y Costilla.</string>
    <string name="info_model_tour">Room 3 Models In this room you will find all kinds of models related to the history of Dolores Hidalgo and how our ancestors lived</string>
    <string name="info_statue_tour">Room 4 Statues In this room you will find a great variety of Statues, some of them are: * Miguel Hidalgo y Costilla * El Pipila</string>
    <string name="info_handicrafts_two">Dolores Hidalgo is one of the main producing centers of traditional majolica tile with decoration of colonial type, from Mexico.</string>
    <string name="info_handicrafts_three">It should be noted that you can not designate ceramics with the word talavera since in 1997 Puebla made formalities before the Mexican Institute of Industrial Property to obtain the denomination of origin.</string>
    <string name="info_handicrafts_one">The tableware * Talavera type with Spanish influence are of high quality, also the typical pottery is made in vases, pots and pitchers, in addition to different ceramic pieces made and decorated by hand</string>
    <string name="dolores">Dolores</string>
    <string name="adult">General</string>
    <string name="young">Student</string>
    <string name="children">Right to take Photo</string>
    <string name="register_costs">Register Costs Tickets</string>
    <string name="name_transition_image">Share image</string>
    <string name="gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="change">Change language</string>
    <string name="str_en">English</string>
    <string name="str_es">Spanish</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="comments">Comentaries</string>
    <string name="audioguide">Audioguide</string>
    <string name="languages">Language</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="idioms">Languages</string>
    <string name="credit">Credit</string>
    <string name="user">User</string>
    <string name="church_name_menu">Church</string>
    <string name="lithography">Litography</string>
    <string name="gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="restaurant">Restaurant</string>
    <string name="video">Video</string>
    <string name="museum">Museum</string>
    <string name="crafts">Crafts</string>
    <string name="ice_cream">Ice Cream</string>
    <string name="halls">Halls</string>
    <string name="memoram">Memory Game</string>
    <string name="logout">Log out</string>
    <string name="cost_ticket">Cost Tickets</string>
    <string name="boys">Children</string>
    <string name="game_bottle">Bottle Game</string>
    <string name="launch">Launch</string>
    <string name="change_idiom">Change Language</string>
    <string name="price">Price</string>
    <string name="audio_guide">Audioguide</string>
    <string name="info_share">"Dare to share the experience lived in Dolores Hidalgo, Magic Town! "</string>
    <string name="description_snow_three">" Ice Cream since 1962. The most common flavors are: Cookie, Cajeta, Drunk, Lemon. They have exotic flavors such as: Gansito, Tequila, Beer"</string>
    <string name="description_snow_two">They started with their great popularity since 1943. The most common flavors are: Vanilla, Walnut, Lemon, Zapote. The most exotic flavors are Tequila,</string>
    <string name="description_snow_one">Ice Cream with more than 30 years of experience and great variety of flavors. The most common flavors you can find are: vanilla, lemon, strawberry, mango and walnut. The most exotic flavors are: Petal of roses, Kiss of Angel, Tequila, Shrimp with octopus and Withe Russian Crackling.. Founded by Josue Morales Hernandez.</string>
    <string name="summary_gallery_five">" Scale model of the Parroquia de Nuestra Señora de los Dolores, was founded on February 2, 1712 by Lic. Alvaro de Osio y Ocampo, the first priest of the Villa de Dolores, formerly Cocomacan or Comacora."</string>
    <string name="summary_gallery_four">" Lithograph of 1807 by unknown author, his original name Maria Josefa Crescencia Ortiz Tellez Gamez de Dominguez"</string>
    <string name="summary_gallery_one">" Lithograph by Ramon Perez, Ignacio Jose de Jesus Pedro Regalado Allende Iunsaga"</string>
    <string name="summary_gallery_two">"Lithograph by Jesús Ramirez, the original painting is in the Alhondiga de Granaditas 'Miguel Gregorio Antonio Ignacio Hidalgo Costilla Gallega Mandarte Villaseñor' "</string>
    <string name="summary_gallery_three">"This lithography dates from the 18th century, it is Miguel Gregorio Antonio Ignacio Hidalgo Costilla Gallega Mandarte Villaseñor at the age of 39, being rector of the College of San Nicolás Obispo Valladolid today Morelia Michoacán Sansän Definiciones de San sustantivo a member of the aboriginal peoples of southern Africa commonly called Bushmen. ‘I knew very well,’ he said, ‘That one did not call someone a San to his face.’ the group of Khoisan languages spoken by the San. San turned out not to be closely related at all. adjetivo relating to the San or their languages. The human rights organisation claimed that the men spoke Secherechere, a San dialect, and at the time of their trial understood neither Setswana (the language of Botswana) nor any language other than their own. "</string>
    <string name="info_church_five">The Temple of Jesus Nazareno began to be built on June 16, 1875. The history of the parish registers tells us that: a neighborhood meeting was held in the neighborhood of \"the band work\" -the south band of the Batán River- to request the Lord Cure Jose Maria Gomez the need to build a temple for spiritual help</string>
    <string name="info_church_four">This Temple was built in 1510., by the hands of the people of the town and directed by the Augustinian friars.</string>
    <string name="info_church_three">After the Parish of Our Lady of Sorrows, it is the oldest religious building in the city, as can be seen in an inscription that appears in the choir\'s arch indicating that it was closed in 1755. Building composed of three naves, its altar Mayor is dedicated to the Virgin of the Immaculate Conception</string>
    <string name="info_church_two">The construction of the Temple of the Assumption of Mary began on May 12, 1875 by order of Mr. Cura Don José María Gómez. Before being named as patron saint under the invocation of the Assumption of Mary, she was venerated as the Virgin of the Saleta</string>
    <string name="info_church_one">The construction of the Parish of Our Lady of Los Dolores began on February 2, 1712 by order of Mr. Cura Lic. Álvaro de Osio y Ocampo and was concluded in the year of 1778. In the year of 1803, Don Miguel Hidalgo and Costilla is in charge of the parish\'s parish and, in the portico of the parish, proclaims the Cry of Independence at dawn on Sunday, September 16, 1810.</string>
    <string name="title_gallery_five">"Parish Model of Nuestra Señora de los Dolores "</string>
    <string name="puzzle">Puzzle</string>
    <string name="not_permission_call">You do not have permission to make phone calls</string>
    <string name="permission_call">You have permission</string>
    <string name="info_fruty">" The Fruty invites you to meet their menu, come to our Restaurant to live an unforgettable experience."</string>
    <string name="info_cost_ticket">" If you want more information about the tickets you can call the staff phone"</string>
    <string name="button_video_two">Places to visit Dolores Hidalgo C.I.N. Gto.</string>
    <string name="button_video_four">Tourism in the Magical Town Dolores Hidalgo</string>
    <string name="button_video_three">" Dolores Hidalgo, Guanajuato. Magic Town"</string>
    <string name="button_video_one">Magic Town Dolores Hidalgo C.I.N. Gto.</string>
    <string name="hall_one">Hall 1 painting</string>
    <string name="hall_two">Hall 2 Photographs</string>
    <string name="hall_three">Hall 3 Models</string>
    <string name="hall_four">Hall 4 Wax statues</string>
    <string name="description_credit">" It is an application to promote tourism in Dolores Hidalgo and the museum: Casa de los Descendientes de Hidalgo."</string>
    <string name="authors_credit">AUTHORS:</string>
    <string name="consultant">CONSULTANT:</string>
    <string name="name_consultant">Eng.: Anastacio Rodríguez García</string>
    <string name="client">CLIENT:</string>
    <string name="name_museum_credit">Museum Casa de los Descendientes de Hidalgo</string>
    <string name="bibliography">BIBLIOGRAPHYS:</string>
    <string name="info_video_five">History Dolores Hidalgo</string>
    <string name="detail_video_five">Learn about the history of the beautiful Magical Town Dolores Hidalgo Cuna de la Independencia Nacional. The video is taken from YouTube, which is copyright: Turismo Dolores Hidalgo</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading...</string>
    <string name="again_play">Again Play</string>
    <string name="cat_game">Cat Game</string>
    <string name="win">The winner is</string>
    <string name="draw">Draw</string>
    <string name="winner">Winner</string>
</resources>